<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gary Yao</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gary Yao</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mother and Lamb</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/photos/nalati-grassland/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/photos/nalati-grassland/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A tender moment between a mother sheep and her lamb on the vast Nalati Grassland in Ili, Xinjiang. The golden evening light bathes the scene in warmth, highlighting the contrast between the white adult sheep and the brown lamb against the lush green meadow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring in Nalati: Life on the Ancient Grasslands</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/nalati-grassland/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/nalati-grassland/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s something profoundly moving about witnessing the cycle of life on one of Asia&amp;rsquo;s most ancient grasslands. During my recent trip to Xinjiang&amp;rsquo;s Ili region, I spent several days exploring the magnificent Nalati Grassland, known locally as the &amp;ldquo;sky grassland&amp;rdquo; for its high elevation and proximity to the clouds.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;April marks the beginning of spring in this region, when the grasslands awaken from their winter dormancy. The timing of my visit couldn&amp;rsquo;t have been more perfect - lambing season was in full swing, offering countless opportunities to observe the tender interactions between mother sheep and their newborns.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tianshan Majesty</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/photos/xinyuan-mountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/photos/xinyuan-mountains/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The magnificent snow-capped peaks of the Tianshan Mountains rise dramatically above the verdant spring grasslands in Xinyuan County. This breathtaking contrast between the lush green meadows and the pristine white mountain range creates one of Xinjiang&amp;rsquo;s most iconic landscapes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Heaven Meets Earth: The Tianshan Range</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/xinyuan-mountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/xinyuan-mountains/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are certain landscapes that seem to exist at the boundary between earth and heaven. The Tianshan Mountains in Xinjiang&amp;rsquo;s Ili region is one such place - a realm where snow-capped peaks pierce blue skies while verdant grasslands spread out below like a green ocean.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During my journey through Xinjiang this April, I was fortunate to witness this spectacular mountain range from Xinyuan County, where the timing of my visit coincided with a perfect weather window after recent spring snowfall.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Tranquility</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/photos/sayram-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/photos/sayram-lake/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The crystal-clear waters of Sayram Lake reflect the azure sky, creating a seamless blend of blues that stretches to the distant mountains. This alpine lake, situated at 2,073 meters above sea level, is the largest and highest alpine lake in Xinjiang, known for its remarkable color that changes throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sapphire of the Tianshan: Sayram Lake</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sayram-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sayram-lake/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a Kazakh legend that tells of a young couple, Sayram and Salimu, whose tears of joy formed a vast lake after they were finally united following years of separation. Standing on the shores of Sayram Lake, surrounded by an almost supernatural blue that seems to pulse with its own inner light, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to understand why such poetic myths would arise around this extraordinary body of water.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During my exploration of Xinjiang in late April 2024, I dedicated a full day to experiencing this alpine gem, known locally as the &amp;ldquo;Last Teardrop of the Atlantic&amp;rdquo; due to the moisture-bearing air currents that travel thousands of kilometers from the Atlantic Ocean to finally release precipitation here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hosting Static Sites on Fly.io</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hosting-static-sites/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hosting-static-sites/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently joined the team at &lt;a href=&#34;https://fly.io&#34;&gt;Fly.io&lt;/a&gt;, and have slowly been moving my various sites and hobby projects over. In case you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of Fly.io, we help developers host apps (all sorts of apps, not only JavaScript-based ones) close to users – no devops skills required. I use Fly.io to host a few Python apps like &lt;a href=&#34;#&#34;&gt;this one&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;#&#34;&gt;this one&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While Fly.io is primarily designed for hosting applications, it&amp;rsquo;s also a great place to host static sites. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to deploy a static site to Fly.io in just a few minutes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Night</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tokyo-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tokyo-night/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tokyo transforms into a completely different world after sunset. The city lights create a mesmerizing landscape that seems straight out of a sci-fi movie.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This photo was taken from Roppongi Hills, looking towards Tokyo Tower. The orange glow of the tower contrasts beautifully with the blue and white lights of the surrounding buildings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;photography-notes&#34;&gt;Photography Notes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shot with Sony A7IV and 16-35mm f/2.8 lens at 24mm. Settings: f/4, 15s, ISO 100.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Tower at Night</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/photos/tokyo-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/photos/tokyo-night/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tokyo skyline at night, with Tokyo Tower illuminated. The orange glow of the tower contrasts beautifully with the blue and white lights of the surrounding buildings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood Moon Eclipse</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/photos/the-moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/photos/the-moon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A &amp;ldquo;blood moon&amp;rdquo; lunar eclipse captured at 840mm (1260mm FF-equivalent).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Moon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-moon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There was a &amp;ldquo;blood moon&amp;rdquo; eclipse tonight. I&amp;rsquo;ve never tried photographing the moon before – mostly because I didn&amp;rsquo;t own a telephoto lens until recently. The photo below was captured at 840mm (1260mm FF-equivalent). It&amp;rsquo;s crazy to think this giant rock is just chilling up there.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The lunar eclipse was visible from North America, and I was lucky enough to have clear skies in my area. I set up my camera on a tripod and used a remote shutter release to minimize camera shake.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shonan Sunset</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/photos/shonan-sunset/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/photos/shonan-sunset/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mt. Fuji at sunset, viewed from Shonan coast. The combination of Mt. Fuji&amp;rsquo;s silhouette against the vibrant orange and red sky creates a truly breathtaking scene.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shonan Sunset</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/shonan-sunset/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/shonan-sunset/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One perk of living in Shonan is being able to see sunsets like this one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The combination of Mt. Fuji&amp;rsquo;s silhouette against the vibrant orange and red sky creates a truly breathtaking scene. On clear days like this, you can see the mountain perfectly from the coast.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;photography-notes&#34;&gt;Photography Notes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This photo was taken with a Sony A7IV and 24-70mm f/2.8 lens at 55mm. Settings: f/8, 1/125s, ISO 100.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I used a graduated ND filter to balance the bright sky with the darker foreground, and waited for the sun to position itself just behind the mountain to create this dramatic effect.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
